<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gamey</title><link>https://gamey.tech/</link><description>Recent content on Gamey</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamey.tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Plasma mobile apps in Phosh</title><link>https://gamey.tech/posts/plasma-mobile-apps-in-phosh/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamey.tech/posts/plasma-mobile-apps-in-phosh/</guid><description>&lt;p>Today I will touch on a topic that I had issues with for a long time till I somewhat figured it out or I at least hope I did. It&amp;rsquo;s not at all hard to do but you have to know what to do and since I found no proper guide or anything about this except for a environment variable &lt;a href="https://github.com/1peter10/linuxphone-tweaks/blob/main/etc/environment" target="_blank" rel="noopener">list&lt;/a> by Peter from linmob I thought I would make my own. I want to clarify that I am not a expert and my experience with Plasma apps is fairly limited but I got the few things that I struggled with together and wrote a quick post that will hopefully help some of you out there! As always all of my testing is done on my 2GB Pinephone running DanctNIX Archlinux mobile and these are things I also did on my PostmarketOS install.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>PINEPHONE: 5 amazing Linux phone apps! Part 3</title><link>https://gamey.tech/posts/pinephone-5-amazing-linux-phone-apps-part-3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamey.tech/posts/pinephone-5-amazing-linux-phone-apps-part-3/</guid><description>&lt;p>Yet another post about five of the in my opinion best Pinephone apps but I promised to make a small series out of this so it&amp;rsquo;s probably not a big surprise. You can find the last two posts linked down below if you are interested in more after this and as always the screenshots and testing where done on my 2GB Pinephone model in DanctNIX mobile Archlinux.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Podcasts on the Pinephone</title><link>https://gamey.tech/posts/podcasts-on-the-pinephone/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamey.tech/posts/podcasts-on-the-pinephone/</guid><description>&lt;p>Today I want to talk about Podcasts on mobile GNU/Linux devices. As one of the last truly free media formats Podcasts are a perfect match with devices like the Pinephone and it&amp;rsquo;s also what I enjoyed most of in terms of content formats on mine. I have to admit that I never really was into Podcasts but lately I discovered that one of my favorite newspapers (Der Falter) has one and from there it just went on with my all time favorite Darknet Diaries which is just fantastic, the Pinetalk and the PostmarketOS podcast. I bet I will discover many more in the future because now I am hooked!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>PINEPHONE: 5 amazing Linux phone apps! Part 2</title><link>https://gamey.tech/posts/pinephone-5-amazing-linux-phone-apps-part-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamey.tech/posts/pinephone-5-amazing-linux-phone-apps-part-2/</guid><description>&lt;p>Today I want to highlight five more of the in my opinion best Pinephone apps in a little more detail. I think I will make a series out of this because I like to do it and apparently people like to read it. As always all of my testing is done on my 2GB Pinephone with DanctNIX Arch Linux.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Browsers on the Pinephone</title><link>https://gamey.tech/posts/browsers-on-the-pinephone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamey.tech/posts/browsers-on-the-pinephone/</guid><description>&lt;p>Today I thought I would do a full rewrite of my Pinephone browsers post because it&amp;rsquo;s obviously a important peace on every phone specially with a limited app selection. I hope this is helpful to some of you and as always all my testing is done on my 2GB Pinephone with DanctNIX Arch Linux.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>My Pinephone Dailydriver setup (Outdated)</title><link>https://gamey.tech/posts/my-pinephone-dailydriver-setup-outdated/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamey.tech/posts/my-pinephone-dailydriver-setup-outdated/</guid><description>&lt;p>Today I will talk a little about my personal Pinephone setup which I use as daily driver by now. Unlike on my testing setup where I just love DanctNIX Arch ARM in this case I chose PostmarketOS. The reason for that is it&amp;rsquo;s minimalist approach which fits perfect for a Alpine base and even better for a low end device like the Pinephone. The main advantage of Arch is the AUR and it&amp;rsquo;s always up to date packages which makes it perfect as a testing setup and for many of your probably also as daily driver but I tend to spend a lot of time for my daily driver setups to get them right once and then use them till I want to change something. I also took PostmarketOS edge since I think stable isn&amp;rsquo;t quite there yet but as soon as I get along with stable I will switch to that. So to sum it up what I use as my current daily driver phone is PostmarketOS edge with my favorite mobile DE Phosh. I can&amp;rsquo;t really say why but I just don&amp;rsquo;t like Plasma mobile in it&amp;rsquo;s current state it somehow feels cheap to me (personal taste). I though it could be useful to some to also include parts of the installation because of the sometimes annoying but awesome Pmbootstrap so this post will probably be a bit longer then my usual ones. As always everything is done on my 2GB RAM Pinephone and may be a tiny bit different on a 3GB version.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>PINEPHONE: 5 amazing Linux phone Apps!</title><link>https://gamey.tech/posts/pinephone-5-amazing-linux-phone-apps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamey.tech/posts/pinephone-5-amazing-linux-phone-apps/</guid><description>&lt;p>Today I thought I would make a small list with some of the in my opinion best Pinephone apps. As always it&amp;rsquo;s done on DanctNIX Arch with Phosh and my 2GB Pinephone and since I don&amp;rsquo;t have a Librem5 I can&amp;rsquo;t say anything specific about it but most of the apps should work across all true mobile GNU/Linux Phones.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Fractal on the Pinephone</title><link>https://gamey.tech/posts/fractal-on-the-pinephone/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamey.tech/posts/fractal-on-the-pinephone/</guid><description>&lt;p>Today I want to take a look at a fantastic Matrix client on the Pinephone and show you workarounds for it&amp;rsquo;s main two issues. Fractal is a awesome Matrix client for Gnome and Phosh but it currently lacks support for encryption and on Phosh it can&amp;rsquo;t open the Gnome Keyring (safe your login). Luckily there are workarounds for those two issues and those are what this post will focus on. If you want to know more about all current options to use Matrix on the Pinephone I made a post about them a while ago which is linked down below.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>