<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ArchLinux on Gamey</title><link>https://gamey.tech/tags/archlinux/</link><description>Recent content in ArchLinux on Gamey</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gamey.tech/tags/archlinux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>PINEPHONE: Matrix clients on Linux Phones!</title><link>https://gamey.tech/posts/pinephone-matrix-clients-on-linux-phones/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamey.tech/posts/pinephone-matrix-clients-on-linux-phones/</guid><description>I actually wrote two articles about this topic ages ago and there has been depressingly little development since then but there have been changes that make the future look a lot brighter. What I am referring to is Matrix support on Linux phones and with that push notifications which essentially don&amp;rsquo;t exist in the current GNU/Linux ecosystem but are a essential component for a good Smartphone. I am probably not the only one who got frustrated by the current state more then once and possibly even lost hope altogether but there is a light at the end of a long tunnel and that&amp;rsquo;s what I want to show you in this article!</description></item><item><title>PINEPHONE: Reddit clients for Linux Phones!</title><link>https://gamey.tech/posts/pinephone-reddit-clients-for-linux-phones/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamey.tech/posts/pinephone-reddit-clients-for-linux-phones/</guid><description>Today I will focus on Reddit clients, yea I know Reddit is big tech but it can be incredibly useful and at least since I started to write articles like this one I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t want to miss it. There are actually quite a few Reddit clients and some of them very nice to so I would say that in this aspect you are absolutely covered as Linux Phone user! As always all of my testing is done on my 2GB Pinephone running DanctNIX Arch Linux and Phosh as DE.</description></item><item><title>PINEPHONE: 5 amazing Linux phone apps!</title><link>https://gamey.tech/posts/pinephone-5-amazing-linux-phone-apps/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamey.tech/posts/pinephone-5-amazing-linux-phone-apps/</guid><description>Today I thought I would make a small list with some of the in my opinion best Pinephone apps. As always it&amp;rsquo;s done on DanctNIX Arch with Phosh and my 2GB Pinephone and since I don&amp;rsquo;t have a Librem5 I can&amp;rsquo;t say anything specific about it but most of the apps should work across all true mobile GNU/Linux Phones.
Note: This is a old article but I rewrote most of it on 07.</description></item><item><title>Podcasts on the Pinephone</title><link>https://gamey.tech/posts/podcasts-on-the-pinephone/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gamey.tech/posts/podcasts-on-the-pinephone/</guid><description>&lt;p>Today I want to talk about Podcasts on mobile GNU/Linux devices. As one of the last truly free media formats Podcasts are a perfect match with devices like the Pinephone and it&amp;rsquo;s also what I enjoyed most of in terms of content formats on mine. I have to admit that I never really was into Podcasts but lately I discovered that one of my favorite newspapers (Der Falter) has one and from there it just went on with my all time favorite Darknet Diaries which is just fantastic, the Pinetalk and the PostmarketOS podcast. I bet I will discover many more in the future because now I am hooked!&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>